press-release.info 2012-05-23

# XooArticles.com - Xoo Article Submission - Submit press release online free of charge

Your privacy is very important to Xooarticles.com. We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe and we take our responsibility seriously to protect the data that you provide us in the normal course of interacting with our site. Therefore, we have developed the comprehensive privacy policy below to help you better understand the manner in which Xooarticles collects , uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of Xooarticles.com and the content, information and services provided through the website Xooarticles.com.

What Information We Collect

We collect two types of information about users as following: 

  * Information that you, users provide through optional, voluntary submissions such as your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, etc. when you register for various services we provide (example: Creating a membership account). These are voluntary submissions to contact an article author, to receive our electronic newsletters, to email a friend, etc.
  * Information that we collect through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs. Under no circumstances do we divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

How we collect and use information

Xooarticles collects personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, etc. when you register for various services we provide (example: Creating a membership account). We may combine this data with other Xooarticles services or 3rd party data to provide a better user experience for you.

We use this information in order to contact you and provide you with further information about our company and services, as well as for other commercial and/or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.

User Tracking

We track user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites to monitor the activities of each unique visitor to Xooarticles. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously, but if you do not register on this Site or fill in your personal details on any forms, you do remain anonymous and we do not discover your identity. If you do register on this Site, our use of user tracking enables us to identify your future and prior activity on the Site, including your activity before you registered. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. User tracking also allows us to determine through which means you have reached our Site (i.e. which search engines or links) up to one web page back. The purpose of our user tracking is to analyze our visitors' actions in order to improve the user experience of visitors to our Site, as well as to better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.

Cookies

Xooarrticles uses cookies that are small text files transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. Even if you do not register on this Site, upon your first visit to this Site (or subsequent visits if you delete the cookie), a cookie is stored on your computer, which automatically identifies you to the Site. We also use other technologies to provide you with a quality experience and to learn how you use our services so that we can continually innovate to improve our services. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. In addition, you can delete any cookies that have already been placed on your computer.

Internet Protocol Addresses. Xooarticelses collects the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above.

Hyperlinks. Xooarticles consists of hyperlinks to other web sites. And this privacy policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. So Xooarticels has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over, the privacy policies of any of these sites.

Your Consent By using the website Xooarticles.com, you are signifying, expressing and providing your consent to the collection and use of the information and other procedures described in the privacy policy above. Xooarticles.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Opt-OutPolicy  
You can decline to submit personal information for any of our services, in which case Xooarticles.com may not be able to provide services to you.

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our web site or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Contact   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, don't hesitate to contact us at contact@xooarticles.com
